<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kajongg.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كونج</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Re Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Каџонг</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Kadžong</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Каџонг</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Kadžong</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKajonggxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kajongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Kajongg</name>
  <summary>Mahjong tile game from China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">لعبة قطع كونج من الصين</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc de fitxes de Mahjong de la Xina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc de fitxes de Mahjong de la Xina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Mahjong-Spiel aus China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Mahjong tile game from China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Mahjong-kahelludo el Ĉinio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego de fichas Mahjong originario de China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Mahjongi klotsimäng Hiinast</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Mahjong Txinako fitxa-jokoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Mahjongg-laattapeli Kiinasta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu de tuiles Mahjong originaire de Chine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xogo de teselas Mahjong da China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">משחק האריחים הסיני מה־ג׳ונג</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Joco de tegula Mahjong ex China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan kartu mahjong dari China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco delle tessere Mahjong dalla Cina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">Mahjong ფილების თამაში ჩინეთიდან</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">중국식 마작 게임</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Spel met Mahjong stenen uit China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Mahjongg-brettspel frå Kina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra przy użyciu Mahjong z Chin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo de peças de Mahjong da China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo de peças Mahjong da China</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Маджонг — игра в кости из Китая</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Dlaždicová hra z Číny Mahjong</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Mahjong je kitajska namizna igra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Mahjong-brickspel från Kina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Çin’den Mahjong masa oyunu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Китайська гра плитками маджонґ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMahjong tile game from Chinaxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">来自中国的麻将牌游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">來自中國的麻將牌遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kajongg is the ancient Chinese board game for 4 players.
      Kajongg can be used in two different ways: Scoring a manual game where you play as always and use Kajongg for the
      computation of scores and for bookkeeping. Or you can use Kajongg to play against any combination of other human players
      or computer players.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">كونج هي لعبة لوحية صينية قديمة لأربعة لاعبين. يمكن استخدام كونج بطريقتين مختلفتين: احتساب أهداف لعبة يدوية حيث تلعب ماجونغ يدويا وتستخدم كونج لحساب الدرجات ولإمساك الدفاتر. أو يمكنك استخدام كونج للعب ضد اللاعبين الآخرين أو ضد الحاسوب.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Kajongg je drevna kineska igra na ploči za 4 igrača. Kajongg se može koristiti na dva različita načina: Igranje ručne igre u kojoj igrate kao i uvijek i koristiti Kajongg za izračunavanje rezultata i za knjigovodstvo. Ili možete koristiti Kajongg igrati protiv bilo koje kombinacije drugih ljudskih igrača ili računarskih igrača.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kajongg és l'antic joc de tauler xinès per a 4 jugadors. El Kajongg es pot usar de dues maneres diferents: Puntuant un joc manual a on jugueu com sempre i useu el Kajongg pel càlcul de les puntuacions i l'enregistrament. O podeu usar el Kajongg per a jugar contra qualsevol combinació d'altres jugadors humans o ordinadors.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kajongg és l'antic joc de tauler xinés per a 4 jugadors. Kajongg es pot utilitzar de dues maneres diferents: Puntuant un joc manual a on jugueu com sempre i utilitzeu Kajongg pel càlcul de les puntuacions i la gravació. O podeu utilitzar Kajongg per a jugar contra qualsevol combinació d'altres jugadors humans o ordinadors.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kajongg ist ein altes chinesisches Brettspiel für 4 Spieler. Es  kann auf zwei Arten verwendet werden: Erstens ein manuelles Spiel bewerten, wo Sie wie immer spielen und Kajongg  für die Berechnung der Punkte und für die Abrechnung verwenden. Zweitens mit Kajongg spielen: gegen eine beliebige Kombination von anderen Personen und Rechnerspielern.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kajongg is the ancient Chinese board game for 4 players. Kajongg can be used in two different ways: Scoring a manual game where you play as always and use Kajongg for the computation of scores and for bookkeeping. Or you can use Kajongg to play against any combination of other human players or computer players.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Kajongg estas la antikva ĉina tabulludo por 4 ludantoj. Kajongg povas esti uzata en du malsamaj manieroj: Poentado de manludo kie vi ludas kiel ĉiam kaj uzas Kajongg por la komputado de poentoj kaj por librotenado. Aŭ vi povas uzi Kajongg por ludi kontraŭ iu ajn kombinaĵo de aliaj homaj ludantoj aŭ komputilaj ludantoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kajongg es un antiguo juego de tablero chino para 4 jugadores. Kajongg puede jugarse de dos maneras distintas: jugar de forma manual y usar Kajongg para los cómputos de la puntuación y las cuentas. O puede usar Kajongg para jugar contra cualquier combinación de jugadores humanos o máquinas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kajongg on muistne Hiina lauamäng neljale mängijale. Kajonggi võib kasutada kahel viisil: mängu tulemuste määramine käsitsi, millisel juhul mäng käib nagu ikka, ilma arvuti abita, ning Kajonggi kasutatakse tulemuste arvutamiseks ja arvepidamiseks. Teine võimalus Kajonggi kasutada on mängida mis tahes inim- ja arvutimängijate kombinatsiooni vastu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kajongg 4 jokalarirentzako Txinako antzinako mahai-jokoa da. Kajongg bi era ezberdinetan erabil daiteke: Eskuz, betiko moduan jokatzen duzun partida baten markagailu gisa, Kajongg puntuazioak eta kontuak eramateko kalkuluak egiteko erabiliz. Edo Kajongg erabil dezakezu edozein giza- edo ordenagailu-jokalari konbinazioren aurka jokatzeko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kajongg on vanha kiinalainen lautapeli neljälle pelaajalle. Kajonggia voi pelata kahdella tapaa: voit joko pelata tavalliseen tapaan ja käyttää Kajonggia vain laskemaan pisteet ja pitämään kirjaa, tai voit pelata mitä tahansa muiden ihmispelaajien ja tietokonepelaajien yhdistelmää vastaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kajongg est un ancien jeu de société chinois pour 4 joueurs. Kajongg peut être utilisé de deux manières : pour calculer les scores et tenir les comptes lors d'une partie manuelle durant laquelle vous jouez comme d'habitude ou bien pour jouer contre d'autres joueurs humains ou contre l'ordinateur par l'intermédiaire de Kajongg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Kajongg é un antigo xogo de taboleiro chinés para 4 xogadores. Kajongg pódese usar de dúas maneiras distintas. Podes xogar unha partida manual na que ti xogas como sempre e empregas Kajongg para que leve a puntuación e as anotacións. Ou podes usar Kajongg para xogar contra calquera combinación de xogadores humanos ou informáticos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Kajongg הוא משחק הלוח הסיני העתיק ל־4 שחקנים. אפשר להשתמש ב־Kajongg בשתי צורות שונות: ניקוד במשחק ידני בו ניתן לשחק כרגיל ולהשתמש ב־ Kajongg לחישוב הניקוד ומצב המשחק. או שאפשר להשתמש ב־Kajongg כדי לשחק נגד מגוון שילובים של שחקנים אנושיים או מחשבים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Kajongg adalah permainan papan Cina kuno untuk 4 pemain. Kajongg dapat digunakan dalam dua cara yang berbeda: Penskoran sebuah permainan manual di mana kamu bermain seperti biasa dan menggunakan Kajongg untuk penghitungan skor dan untuk pembukuan. Atau kamu bisa menggunakan Kajongg untuk bermain melawan kombinasi pemain manusia lain atau pemain komputer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kajongg è l'antico gioco cinese da tavolo per quattro giocatori. Kajongg può essere usato in due modi differenti: conteggio dei punti di una partita manuale, in cui giochi come al solito ma utilizzi Kajongg per contare e registrare i punti. Oppure puoi usarlo per giocare contro una qualsiasi combinazione di persone e computer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Kajongg უძველესი ჩინური სამაგიდო თამაშია, 4 კაცისთვის. Kajongg შეგიძლიათ, ორნაირად ითამაშოთ. გაასწრობანა მორგებულ თამაშში, სადაც თქვენ, როგორც ყოველთვის, ისე თამაშობთ და Kajongg-ს მხოლოდ ქულების დასათვლელად და სანიშნებისთვის იყენებთ, ან იყენებთ Kajongg-ს, რომ ითამაშოთ ნებისმიერი კომბინაციით ადამიანის თუ კომპიუტერის მოთამაშეების წინააღმდეგ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Kajongg은 4인용 고대 중국식 보드 게임입니다. 현실 세계의 게임의 점수를 관리하거나, 사람이나 컴퓨터 플레이어로 게임을 즐길 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kajongg is het oude Chinese bordspel voor 4 spelers. Kajongg kan op twee verschillende manieren worden gebruikt: de score bijhouden van een handmatig spel waar u speelt zoals u gewend bent en u gebruikt Kajongg voor het berekenen van de scores en voor bijhouden van de boeken. Of u kunt Kajongg gebruiken om tegen elke combinatie van andere menselijke spelers of computerspelers te spelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Kajongg er det klassiske, kinesiske brettspelet Mahjong for fire spelarar. Du kan spela på to måtar: 2) vanleg speling mot menneske og/eller datamotstandarar, eller 2) poengteljing for eit manuelt parti, der du spelar som vanleg og brukar Kajongg for å rekna ut poenga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kajongg jest starożytną, chińską grą planszową dla 4 graczy. Kajongg można używać na dwa różne sposoby: Punktacja ręcznej gry, gdzie grasz jak zwykle i używasz Kajongg do obliczania punktów. Można też użyć Kajongg do grania przeciwko dowolnej kombinacji innych graczy ludzkich lub sterowanych przez komputer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kajongg é o antigo jogo chinês de tabuleiro para 4 jogadores. O Kajongg pode ser usado de duas diferentes formas: A pontuação de um jogo manual, onde poderá jogar como sempre, e usar o Kajongg como calculadora de pontos e para registo posterior. Poderá ainda usar o Kajongg para jogar contra uma combinação qualquer de outros jogadores humanos ou por computador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Kajongg é o antigo jogo de tabuleiro chinês para 4 jogadores. O Kajongg pode ser usado de duas diferentes formas: A pontuação de um jogo manual, onde poderá jogar como sempre, e usar o Kajongg como calculadora de pontos e para registro posterior. Poderá ainda usar o Kajongg para jogar contra uma combinação qualquer de outros jogadores humanos ou por computador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Kajongg — древняя китайская настольная игра для 4 игроков. Есть два варианта работы с Kajongg. Можно играть в игру обычным способом, используя Kajongg для подсчёта очков и ведения записей об игре. Также Kajongg можно использовать для игры с произвольной комбинацией игроков-людей и компьютерных игроков.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kajongg je stará čínska dosková hra pre 4 hráčov. Kajongg sa dá použiť dvoma odlišnými spôsobmi: Bodovanie ručnej hry, kde hráte ako vždy a použite Kajongg na výpočet bodov a na účtovníctvo. Alebo môžete použiť Kajongg na hranie proti kombinácii iného ľudského hráča alebo počítačových hráčov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kajongg je starodavna kitajska namizna igra za štiri igralce. Kajongg lahko uporabite na dva načina: kot vmesnik za ročno igro, kjer igrate kot običajno in uporabite Kajongg za izračun rezultatov in njihovo shranjevanje ali pa kot vmesnik za igro proti katerikoli kombinaciji človeških ali računalniških igralcev.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Каџонг је древна кинеска игра на табли за четири играча. Каџонг се може користити на два начина. Један је оцењивање ручне игре, где играте као и обично док вам Каџонг служи за израчунавање резултата и праћење. Или можете у Каџонгу заиграти против комбинације других људских и рачунарских играча.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Kadžong je drevna kineska igra na tabli za četiri igrača. Kadžong se može koristiti na dva načina. Jedan je ocenjivanje ručne igre, gde igrate kao i obično dok vam Kadžong služi za izračunavanje rezultata i praćenje. Ili možete u Kadžongu zaigrati protiv kombinacije drugih ljudskih i računarskih igrača.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Каџонг је древна кинеска игра на табли за четири играча. Каџонг се може користити на два начина. Један је оцењивање ручне игре, где играте као и обично док вам Каџонг служи за израчунавање резултата и праћење. Или можете у Каџонгу заиграти против комбинације других људских и рачунарских играча.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Kadžong je drevna kineska igra na tabli za četiri igrača. Kadžong se može koristiti na dva načina. Jedan je ocenjivanje ručne igre, gde igrate kao i obično dok vam Kadžong služi za izračunavanje rezultata i praćenje. Ili možete u Kadžongu zaigrati protiv kombinacije drugih ljudskih i računarskih igrača.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kajongg är det uråldriga kinesiska brädspelet för fyra spelare. Kajongg kan användas på två olika sätt: Poängsätta ett manuellt spel där du spelar som vanligt utan hjälp av en dator och använder Kajongg för att beräkna poäng och bokföring. Eller kan du använda Kajongg för att spela mot vilken kombination som helst av mänskliga eller datorspelare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kajongg, 4 oyuncuyla oynanan eski bir Çin masa oyunudır. Kajongg iki farklı şekilde kullanılabilir: Her zamanki gibi elle oynadığınız oyunu puanlayın ve puanların hesaplanması, defter tutma için Kajongg kullanın. Ya da Kajongg’u diğer canlı oyuncuların veya bilgisayar oyuncularının herhangi bir kombinasyonuna karşı oynamak için kullanabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kajongg — давня китайська гра на дошці для 4 гравців. Kajongg можна користуватися у два різних способи. Можна зіграти у гру у звичний спосіб, а потім скористатися Kajongg для обчислення рахунків та ведення записів щодо гри. Крім того, ви можете скористатися Kajongg для гри з довільною кількістю інших гравців-людей або комп’ютерних гравців.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKajongg is the ancient Chinese board game for 4 players. Kajongg can be used in two different ways: Scoring a manual game where you play as always and use Kajongg for the computation of scores and for bookkeeping. Or you can use Kajongg to play against any combination of other human players or computer players.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Kajongg 是傳統的四人玩的中國式麻將遊戲。Kajongg 有兩種模式進行遊戲：手動記分或是讓 Kajongg 記分。您也可以用 Kajongg 來對抗其他人類或電腦玩家。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kajongg</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kajongg</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kajongg</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kajongg&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">يعلب كونج</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Jugant a Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hraní Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Kajongg spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Playing Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ludante Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugando a Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Kajonggi mängimine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kajongg jokatzea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kajonggin pelaaminen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">En train de jouer à Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xogando a Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">משחק ב־Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Jocar Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Memainkan Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Giocare con Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Kajongg-ის თამაში</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Kajongg 플레이</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Kajongg spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Spelar Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Granie w Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogo do Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogando Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Игра в Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hranie Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Igra Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kajongg Oynama</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у Kajongg</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying Kajonggxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">正在进行麻将游戏</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Kajongg 遊玩畫面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kajongg/kajongg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kajongg.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>kajongg</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
</component>
